The last coding task that we did for the mewalk app involved
تنطوي آخر مهمة تشفير أجريناها لتطبيق لغة ميوك
releasing the media player resources as soon as we didn't need them anymore.
على إفلات موارد مشغل الوسائط بمجرد عدم الحاجة إليها.
But we can't always assume that the audio file will be played to completion.
ولكن لا يمكننا افتراض أن الملف الصوتي سيتم تشغيله حتى النهاية.
Because if it's interrupted by the user switching away to a different activity
وذلك لأنه إذا انقطع بسبب انتقال المستخدم إلى نشاط آخر
then we still need to make sure to clean up everything properly.
فنحن بحاجة إلى الانتظار للتأكد من تنظيف كل شيء على نحوٍ صحيح.
So my question to you is that if the user leaves the activity,
ولذا سؤالي لك الآن هو، ماذا لو ترك المستخدم النشاط
during which activity lifecycle stage should we release resources
في أثناء إفلات الموارد
used by the MediaPlayer?
المستخدمة عن طريق مشغل الوسائط؟
So is it during onResume, onCreate OnStop or onDestroy?
ماذا لو حدث ذلك أثناء حالة onResume أو onCreate أو OnStop أو onDestroy؟
So once you've made your selection, modify your app so
ولذا بمجرد تحديد اختيارك، قم بتعديل التطبيق
that we can actually release resources during that lifecycle stage.
كي نتمكن فعليًا من إفلات الموارد أثناء مرحلة دورة حياة النشاط.
So let me show you what your app should look like before and
ولذا دعني أنظر كيف سيبدو تطبيقك قبل وبعد
after making this code change.
إجراء تغييرات الكود هذه.
So your app currently behaves like this.
وبالتالي يتصرف التطبيق بهذه الطريقة.
If I click on a word, it'll start speaking the word aloud, and
عند النقر على اي كلمة، ستبدأ في نطق الكلمة بصوت عالٍ،
if I leave the activity without letting it finish,
وإذا تركت النشاط دون تركها حتى تنتهي،
the app will still continue to play the full audio file.
سيستمر التطبيق في تشغيل الملف الصوتي بأكمله.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[BLANK_AUDIO]
&gt;&gt; So, here's the version of the code where we cleaned up media resources
&gt;&gt; ها هو إصدار الكود المستخدم في تنظيف موارد الوسائط
properly according to the activity lifecycle.
على نحوٍ صحيح وفقًا لدورة حياة النشاط.
So, in this case, when we hit the device home button.
وبالتالي، في هذه الحالة، عند الضغط على زر الصفحة الرئيسية للجهاز،
The app should immediately stop playing the audio file,
يجب أن يتوقف التطبيق فورًا عن تشغيل الملف الصوتي،
even in the middle of a word.
حتى وإن كان في منتصف الكلمة.
This reinforces the fact that we should only play audio
وهذا يعزز حقيقة وجوب تشغيل الصوت فقط
when the user is within our app.
عندما يكون المستخدم في التطبيق.
Because in our case, we are a music or podcast player app.
وذلك لأن التطبيق هو مشغل موسيقى.
So let me demonstrate.
لذلك، اسمح لي أن أوضح.
[SOUND].
[SOUND].
All right so go ahead and make those code changes now.
حسنًا، سنستمر ونقوم بإجراء تغييرا الكود هذه الآن.
And remember to update all four of our activities.
وتذكر تحديث جميع الأنشطة الأربعة.